{
  "questions": [
    {
      "id": 1,
      "prompt": "What special prop should always be included for lists of elements?",
      "answers": [
        "id",
        "name",
        "key",
        "prop"
      ],
      "correctIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "id": 2,
      "prompt": "A React component is a function that returns ______.",
      "answers": [
        "HTML",
        "JSX",
        "props",
        "state"
      ],
      "correctIndex": 1
    },
    {
      "id": 3,
      "prompt": "Which event handler will run when a user is finished filling out a form?",
      "answers": [
        "onSubmit",
        "onClick",
        "onChange",
        "onForm"
      ],
      "correctIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "id": 4,
      "prompt": "______ is a tool that transpiles JSX into valid JavaScript.",
      "answers": [
        "React",
        "Babel",
        "Webpack",
        "ES6"
      ],
      "correctIndex": 1
    },
    {
      "id": 5,
      "prompt": "What syntax makes it possible to unpack values from arrays, or properties from objects, into distinct variables?",
      "answers": [
        "spread",
        "key-value",
        "coalescing",
        "destructuring"
      ],
      "correctIndex": 3
    },
    {
      "id": 6,
      "prompt": "Returning different elements from a component depending on the state of your application is known as _____ rendering.",
      "answers": [
        "voodoo",
        "conditional",
        "reactive",
        "controlled"
      ],
      "correctIndex": 1
    },
    {
      "prompt": "What is a cat",
      "answers": [
        "rept",
        "amph",
        "mam",
        "bird"
      ],
      "correctIndex": 2,
      "id": 9
    },
    {
      "prompt": "JSX",
      "answers": [
        "html",
        "python",
        "javascript,XML",
        "Javascript,HTML"
      ],
      "correctIndex": 2,
      "id": 10
    },
    {
      "prompt": "Who is a woman",
      "answers": [
        "A weak Person",
        "An object",
        "A cleaner",
        "A hoe"
      ],
      "correctIndex": 3,
      "id": 11
    },
    {
      "prompt": "WHY isnt it worjking",
      "answers": [
        "dk",
        "why",
        "no care",
        "plz work"
      ],
      "correctIndex": 0,
      "id": 12
    }
  ]
}